FROM ME TO YOU 2ND SEASON
MISUNDERSTOOD
Remember what I told you
before... Don't worry about it.
Forget what I said.
I wonder what he meant by that.
That it wasn't anything important
enough for me to even worry about?
Of course it's not.
If I take the time to think about it,
it's really just common sense. It should
be obvious, but still...
You know, I always assumed that at
least out of all the other guys, I was the
closest with you. But maybe I was wrong?
That moment flashed through my mind, over
and over... and I couldn't help but wonder
how I should've responded.
In the end I never
figured out the answer, but...
Forget what I said.
It shouldn't bother me.
And it isn't right... for me to be upset.
I feel foolish...
I keep looking for a deeper meaning in
what he says... But I'm the one worrying.
How embarrassing.
So? You got me here. What do you need?
Hey, chill out!
It's just, you and I are classmates now
and all, and I wanna talk to super popular
Kazehaya too! Come, come. Sit with me!
I don't know how I'm
supposed to feel about that.
Don't worry! Just sit
down and chat with me!
So? I'm sure at least a few girls have
asked you out by now, haven't they? Got a
- girlfriend?
- No, I don't.
You can tell me!
No, seriously. What?
HAIR LOSS THERAPEUTIC
So, Sadako... She's been an
outcast since 1st year, right?
I'm thinking you should cut down on your
interactions with her just a little bit. I
know people like that are hard for you to
ignore, but I think it just makes things
worse.
What does that mean?
That I see her as an outcast? And I can't
ignore outcasts? No, I've never looked at
her like that.
My bad! I must've
struck a nerve somehow, huh?
Hey now! No need to be mad, okay? Let's
see that charming smile you're so famous
- for!
- Either way, you don't
get to speak for me, Miura!
Still, whenever I look at
her, I feel sorry for her.
You should really give her more space.
She's finally starting to blend into
class. But if you get too involved... and
the other girls start to get jealous...
won't she be right back where she started?
Then, all your efforts would
have been pointless, right?
Don't cause her more trouble.
Really? And who are you to tell me that?
Hm?
So, what? If that ever happens, I'll
figure out how to handle it myself! I've
got my own reasons to do the things I do!
What the hell would you know about it?!
Just saying... It's going to lead to more
jealousy... which will lead to her being
more isolated. She's holding onto
such unrealistic expectations. It's sad.
Why do you keep talking
about how you pity her?
Kuronuma is... working hard.
When has she ever had...
"unrealistic expectations"?
That's the thing. You'll never be able to
understand that part. 'Cause that's where
you and Sadako... clearly
have totally different views.
Well, you're in such a different
position than her. How could you
- understand?
- What?!
Can't say any more than that. It's
not for me to give away all of her true
feelings.
You don't wanna make problems for her,
right? Since she's been working so hard.
I know that!
If you know, then cool. You've got this.
Hey, so... the girls like you but
you're not dating one. Ya got a crush?
Yeah, I do!
Then why don't you just go out with her
already?! Or do you want me to help you
- out?
- No! Absolutely not!
What was that about?!
Well, you're in such a different
position than her. How could you
- understand?
- Can't understand what?
And "far from hers?" How?
What's that mean?
W- What do you think?
Looks good!
Seriously? Alright! Tell me a
little more! C'mon, it won't hurt, right?
Yeah. Dead serious.
You look gorgeous, okay?
Oh... So, it's basically a
family only wedding then?
Uh-huh! I guess they're not
even inviting any coworkers.
So, I thought, "Ah... in that
case I'm not going either," but...
Did he?
Mmhm. Toru called me up and asked me
personally; "Chii, I definitely want you
- to be there."
- Ooh! Looks like you're part
of their family after all!
- Were you happy?
- Obviously!
But also, If I'm gonna go, I figure I
should look as cute as possible y'know?
Yeah, that part's pretty important.
And with that dress, you
have got nothing to worry about.
Yup!
Hey!
- Yoshida.
- I happened to have some extra cash
on me, so I had myself an impulse buy!
And Yano-chin sure does have an eye
for this kinda stuff! Man, I wish Sawako
could've seen me with this on!
Speaking of which, did she go home
already?
Yeah, probably.
Hm? What's the deal with
the weirdly vague answer?
H-Hey. Are me and
Kuronuma... super different?
Like... That I maybe don't
understand her as much as I thought I did?
Huh? Course you don't understand her.
I mean, this guy's so clueless, he somehow
doesn't even know that Sawako likes him.
- Where's this coming from?
- N-Nowhere. It's nothing I just
had someone tell me that, so...
Your shoelaces are untied.
Well, it's just that I never
thought that about myself.
In fact, it threw me off because I
thought that I understood her better than
everyone else.
] Let's see... Well, it's kinda hard to
put into words, but like with me and
Yano-chin... we get misunderstood a
lot, though not as much as Sawako.
And we've had people talk a lotta trash
about us. Ryu too. you know how he's been
the cleanup hitter since 1st year?
I guess in the beginning he was treated
pretty rough by his upperclassmen for it.
Makes sense.
So in that aspect... yeah... you might not
be the closest to her... You just haven't
gotten past that.
See ya.
But still where'd that come from?
Did something happen between
him and Sawako? Who knows.
- Sawako put on a whole lecture?
- Yeah, I heard she made
everything easy to understand.
That's so like Kazehaya to put
something like that together for her.
But he wasn't the one who did it though.
Yeah, so you remember that
one really sketchy flirty guy?
His name is Kento!
Apparently, he suddenly blurted out
an invitation in the middle of class.
Miura...
G- Good. Good morning...
Don't overthink it! Just
keep it casual! I-I can't!
Morning.
- Joe!
- Oh hey! What's up?
I'm clearly wrong.
Actually... this is how it always is.
It's... really kinda normal for us,
but... it does feel like he's avoiding me
I must've gotten a big head.
Uh... What?
What's going on?!
Yesterday, when we left, what the heck
did you and Kazehaya talk about to make
things so awkward
between you? Spit it out!
F- From the outside, this
totally looks like bullying.
In other words, you had two
separate conversations with him...
You know I had assumed. Out of all the
guys in class, I was the closest to you.
Oh, forget about what I said before.
- So that's basically what happened then?
- Uh-huh.
He's finally reached his limit.
First of all, why did you give chocolates
to everybody except Kazehaya, Sawako?! You
guys had such a great
thing going up until then!
I mean, the two of you even went to visit
the shrine together on New Year's Eve! You
could've just given them as a
thank-you gift like you usually do!
He gave you his cell phone number so you
could text him and stuff too, didn't he?
Huh? -Hey now, Yano-chin! -No, if you want
one on one time with him, or a chance to
give him your chocolates, just make up
any excuse you can think of, any time, and
it'll work!
- Whoa!
- Whoa! Aw jeez.
Oh no... I'm sorry.
That's not it. I just feel so
lost. I don't know what to do anymore.
I couldn't honestly give him those
chocolates... as if he's just a friend. And
contacting him is out
of the question now.
I'm so self-conscious at this point I
can't even greet him properly anymore. I'm
scared.
It's embarrassing. I
don't want him to hate me.
My true desires... my
greed... I can't hide them.
You might be scared. But I know for
sure that you're not the only one.
Hey, Sawako? Do you want
to stay this way forever?
Cause if you let your fear stop you.
This stressful situation'll go on and on
forever. If you don't want that, then
you'll have to do something about it
- yourself.
- Ayane... Chizu...
I'll never ever be able to thank you
for everything you've both done for me.
You probably won't figure
out what to do right away, so...
Take a deep breath for
now and think it over.
Okay.
- It's you?
I didn't know what to do when Sawako
started crying back there, but you handled
that like a pro. Honestly,
your words even touched me.
Know that guy Nakamura
in the class next door?
- Yeah?
- The other day--
Ow! What was that for?!
Well I could ask you the same! Just
knock it off! It's gone too far. The whole
"avoiding Sawako" thing you're doing.
- Huh?
- I'm lost.
Yeah.
But I'm not!
Even if that's the case, you're definitely
making it look like you're avoiding her!
Remember, she's used to people treating
her like that. So, you need to stop doing
things that might
give her the wrong idea.
See ya.
Uh, wait, Yano-chin!
Everyone has an opinion these days. I
guess it's open season on Kazehaya, huh?!
Sounds like a rough day.
What's going on? You've
been in a really bad mood.
You're right. I was wrong
for taking my anger out on him.
Anger about what?
To be honest, I do also feel at least a
little bit sorry for Kazehaya since he's
- going through a lot too...
- Huh? I don't get it,
why feel sorry for him?
Because if the girl he likes starts
acting super scared of him like that
- then--
- Kazehaya has a girl he likes?!
T-That's not good. Sawako...
But come on Yano-chin, if you really think
about it, he has to be at least a little
bit interested in her, doesn't he? I mean
like yesterday! We had this whole entire
- thing where he...
- Wait. Chill out, Chizu.
So Kazehaya likes Sawa--?! Then
there's not a problem, is there?
Quiet! You don't need to scream! That's
why I'm saying there's no reason for any
of this! What?! That's awesome! But we
shouldn't keep it to ourselves, let's tell
them!
Kazehaya! Good news!
Hold it!
Does he seem to you like the type that
would appreciate other people getting all
- involved in his business?
- N-Now that you mention it...
Back in middle school...
Hey Kazehaya, Eri was telling
me earlier she really likes you.
Stop joking.
I'm serious.
If that's the case, why isn't she the
one telling me this instead of you? It
- doesn't make any sense.
- Ugh, that's about right.
Ah! I can't believe I almost did that! If
we tell him about how Sawako feels and he
thinks she put us up to it,
it's only gonna make things worse!
In that case, we'll just tell Sawako and
have her ask him out! Sawa! Good news!
Hold it!
Sure, we could tell her everything we
know and force her to make a move... And
after that, it's possible that they would
start dating. But is that really how this
should go?
Even if... she continues to be
terrified of what he thinks? Sure, they
might technically end up "going out"
but the actual situation wouldn't be any
different.
- Yeah, but...
- Here's the thing. I don't want Sawako
to have some kind of inferiority complex
while she's going out with him.
That's why I want her to build up her
confidence until she has the will to ask
him out on her own.
Wouldn't it suck? When you're both
supposed to like each other, and one
person thinks the other is
just with them out of pity.
Yeah.
I guess if you think about it, even if
we did end up telling Sawako that Kazehaya
likes her, I'm pretty sure
she'd never believe us anyway.
They're being so
considerate of my feelings.
That's true.
But that doesn't change
what I said... yesterday.
Oh, if we're talking about Sawako... Well,
of course you don't understand her in that
aspect, you might be
the furthest from her.
The one who didn't understand... was me!
So anyway, you were saying
something about him yesterday?
A-About who? I didn't say anything
about Kazehaya-who? I mean, what?
Crap! I gotta do something about
this fast or Yano-chin's gonna kill me!
You went to the cursed lecture?
How was it?
It was insane, dude!
Uh-huh! The rumors were true!
If I were to give an example... let me see...
It's kinda like losing 5 kilos within 3
- days! Yeah, like that!
- S-Say what?!
Th- That sounds like
some kind of disease! Oh no!
Sadako's amazing, huh?!
- Hey they're complimenting you!
- Sada...
Awesome!
You're seriously incredible, Sadako!
- Can you do it again?
- Can I get a passing score in 3 days too?
I want in too!
You see?
Have some more faith in yourself.
Hey, Sadako.
- Thanks so much for yesterday.
- No! It was my pleasure!
By the way, I was wondering, that plant
you gave me the other day where'd you get
- it?
- That was a medicinal herb that
- I'm growing in the flower beds.
- Seriously?
Here at school?
Yes! I carefully selected a
mixture of herbs with various benefits...
Well, it really made a huge difference.
Just saying, it's going to lead to more
jealousy, which will lead to her being
more isolated.
I don't get it.
He's the only person...
My eyes keep avoiding.
Next time: "The Person That I Like"